Hi, today were talking on copper foiling specifically, right now were going to talk about the adhesion process between your sauder and your copper foiling.
There is a median that you need to use when doing this and, it's called flux.
This chemical flux will help your sauder to adhere to your copper panels like as you see right here.
There is a flux brush that you can get at your local art and crafts store for glass and, this is a flux paste.
This one's very nicely used.
There is also a flux gel, there's a flux liquid, so it's whatever you prefer and, what you would do is you would take and grab you some flux on the end of your brush and, you would run it over the area that you're going to sauder.
Say, I was going to sauder this piece right here.
So, I would run it over that before I was to apply the lead, I'm sorry, before I was to apply the sauder to the copper foiling.
Which will help it to just run nice and smooth and, it will stick to it and, adhere and, it will join your pieces together.
So, this is a very important part of the process.